adgeco.com 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Adgeco Group of Companies | Holding Company

****_(Last updated July 9, 2013)_

To underscore our commitment to privacy and our vision to good business, this Online Privacy Policy is adopted for our website, including third party websites but not limited to adgeco.com.  
This governing policy only applies to information collected through our websites and will not apply to information collected in any other mechanisms, including information collected offline.

 **ACCEPTABLE USE**

For any reason that causes, or may cause, damage to the website or impairment of the availability or accessibility of the website; or in any way which is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful, or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity, any user must not use this website.

You must not use this website to copy, host, send, use, , store, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, root kit or other malicious computer software.

You must not execute any methodical data collection activities, including but not limited to scraping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting in relation to this website without ADGECO Group’s express written consent.

 **ONWARD TRANSFER**

If you choose to make information available from our website to other people through group chats, instant messaging, electronic mail messages, blog postings, your networking profile (if any), registering for an event, or by joining groups or using other networking functions that are offered on other websites, this information will be visible to the receiving parties. Please take care in deciding what information you choose to make available through these ways, as we do not control the manner in which recipients or persons who may see the information may use or re-disclose the information that you choose to provide.  
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to comply with the law or legal process or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations proceedings.

 **RESTRICTED ACCESS**

Access in all areas of this website is restricted. ADGECO Group reserves the right to restrict access to this website.

Only ADGECO Group reserves the right to edit or remove any material submitted to this website, or stored on ADGECO servers, or hosted or published upon this website.  
**OTHER WEBSITES**

This Online Privacy Policy only applies to our websites. For your convenience, we may offer links to online tools which allow you to share content from our website with third parties or sites of your choosing, such as LinkIn, Facebook, or Twitter and/or other networking sites, such icons reflected just above the bottom section of the page. Your use of such tools, sometimes called “widgets,” is subject to the privacy policy applicable to the tool or widget that you use.

 **POLICY CHANGES**

We may revise this Online Privacy Policy from as the need arise, any time. If we make any material changes to any part of the Online Privacy Policy, the most recent date of revision will be indicated above so that you can determine whether there have been any material revisions since your last visit.
